{
    "subject": "Louis_IX_of_France",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Margaret_of_Provence",
    "human_readable": "Louis IX of France is married to Margaret of Provence.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9684942364692688,
            "question": "Who was king of France during the marriage of Louis IX and Margaret of Provence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9563415050506592,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Louis IX of France and Margaret of Provence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9340853095054626,
            "question": "Who was Louis IX of France married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9314762949943542,
            "question": "Was Louis IX of France married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8621392250061035,
            "question": "What was the name of the French monarch who married Margaret of Provence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8339471220970154,
            "question": "To whom was Margaret of Provence married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7799515724182129,
            "question": "Who is Margaret of Provence known for being married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7766311168670654,
            "question": "What is the name of Louis IX of France's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5008999109268188,
            "question": "What is Louis IX's wife's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46370929479599,
            "question": "Name the queen consort of Louis IX of France."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Louis IX of France is married to Margaret of Provence.",
            "html": "yago_27294_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Louis IX's wife's name?",
            "html": "yago_27294_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Louis IX of France's wife?",
            "html": "yago_27294_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Margaret of Provence known for being married to?",
            "html": "yago_27294_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27294_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27294_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27294_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27294_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27294_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27294_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27294_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27294_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27294_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27294_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Margaret of Provence was the wife of Louis IX, confirming that Louis IX of France is indeed married to Margaret of Provence."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}